Blair and Lee Family Papers, 1640-1946 (bulk 1812-1920 ): Finding Aid C0614
Manuscripts Division
- Papers of Blair Lee, 1740-1946; 1857-1925; 218 boxes (1 partial)
  - Correspondence, 1740-1930; 84 boxes
    - Family, 1740-1924; 16 boxes
      - Miscellaneous Family Members: A-Z, 1740-1924; 5 boxes
        - Lee, John F. (1848- ), 1888-1924; 2 folders (Box 281, Folder 9-10)
          Includes 3 ALsS, 1891-1892; 90 TLsS, 1888-1924; TLS, 1907, by F. S. Bell to J. F. Lee; 9 telegrams, 1890-1918; 5 telegrams, undated; ALS (copy), 1915, by Blair Lee to J. F. Lee; TLsS (carbons), 1890, to Palmer Trimble; TLS, 1912, by Dwight F. Davis to John F. Lee.
        - Lee, Julia T. - R. H. Lee, 1872-1913; 1 folder (Box 281, Folder 11)
        - Lee, Samuel Phillips (1812-1897), 1897 June; 1 folder (Box 282, Folder 1)
          Consists of letters and telegrams of sympathy from family and friends on S. P. L.'s death.
        - Lee, Sara L., 1894-1919; 2 folders (Box 282, Folder 2-3)
          Includes 62 ALsS, 1894-1919; 41 ALsS, undated; ACsS, 1915; 17 TLsS, 1899-1908; 5 TLsS, undated; TLS, undated, to Arthur Crisfield; TLS, 1918, to S. L. L. by Carroll Pierce.
        - Lee, William H., 1881-1921; 1 folder (Box 282, Folder 4)
          Includes 4 ALsS, 1881-1909; 27 TLsS, 1892-1919; 2 telegrams, 1903-1911; telegram, undated; TLS (carbon), 1921, by Blair Lee to W. H. Lee; TLS, 1904, to J. J. Turner by W. H. Lee with AN, 1904, by Blair Lee; TLS, 1904, by J. J. Turner to W. H. Lee.
        - Lee forebears - Mary Lee Lloyd, 1740-1902; 1 folder (Box 282, Folder 5)
        - McKim, Anne Clymer Brooke, 1893-1919; 1 folder (Box 282, Folder 6)
        - McKim, Randolph Harrison, 1894-1913; 1 folder (Box 282, Folder 7)
          Includes 6 ALsS, 1894-1913; ACS, 1906; ALsS, 1905, to Robert E. Brooke; printed sermon, 1913; 3 printed letters, 1908; printed letter re Dr. McKim, 1908; calling card.
        - Mordecai, Laura - Rosa Mordecai, 1902-1920; 1 folder (Box 282, Folder 8)
        - Moses, Horace: 26 ALsS, 1876-1890; ALS (draft), 1879, by Blair Lee; 3 telegrams, 1876-1892; 1 folder (Box 282, Folder 9)
        - P - Ri (general), 1895-1912; 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 1)
        - Robinson, Alexander Galt, 1893-1920; 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 2)
          Includes 20 ALsS, 1893-1918; 5 TLsS, 1897-1920; 2 telegrams, 1897-1898; ALS, 1893, by James R. Green to Alexander G. Robinson; 2 TLsS, 1893, by L.F. Chipley.
        - Robinson, A. H. - Robinson, P., 1883-1911; 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 3)
        - S - W (general), 1775-1919; 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Political: A-Z, 1860-1925; 22 boxes
      Contains letters to individuals and organizations involved in local state and national politics and election campaigns, and from persons seeking political favors.
      - Abbott - Adler, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 1)
      - Advertiser - Alexander, 1896-1917; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 2)
      - Alleghany County: regarding Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 3)
      - Alleghany Trades - American Red Cross, 1899-1918; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 4)
      - American Society... - Anne Arundel Co., 1900-1923; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 5)
      - Anne Arundel County: regarding Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 6)
      - Anti-Saloon League of Maryland, 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 7)
      - Applegate - Archer, 1899-1915; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 8)
      - Armstrong, John S, 1912-1913; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 9)
      - Ashe - Ayers, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 10)
      - B. P. - Baldwin, Charles G., 1895-1917; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 1)
      - Baldwin, Joseph S., 1911-1913; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 2)
      - City of Baltimore, 1908-1919; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 3)
      - City of Baltimore: regarding Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 4)
      - County of Baltimore: regarding Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 5)
      - County of Baltimore: miscellaneous, 1900-1914; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 6)
      - Baltimore, Board of Trade - "Baltimore World", 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 7)
      - Baltz - Barker, 1898-1914; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 8)
      - Barnard, Fuller, 1900-1917; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 9)
      - Barnard, John - Beall, 1909-1915; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 10)
      - Beau - Billmeyer, 1896-1915; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 11)
      - Birgfeld - Blackburn, 1910-1913; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 12)
      - Blagden, Thomas, 1892-1904; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 13)
      - Blair - Bonifant, 1903-1913; 1 folder (Box 285, Folder 14)
      - Booker - Bradford, H. B., 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 1)
      - Bradford, H. L, 1911-1913; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 2)
      - Bradley - Brooke, 1901-1913; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 3)
      - Brooklyn - Browning, 1899-1913; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 4)
      - Brown & Brune, 1895-1914; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 5)
      - Bruce - Bryan, William H., 1912-1913; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 6)
      - Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925; 2 folders
        - Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 7)
        - Bryan, William Jennings, Clubs, 1860-1925; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 8)
      - Bryan and Sewall Receptions, 1896-1906; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 9)
      - Buck - Burns, 1894-1917; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 10)
      - Byington, Frank D., 1900-1913; 1 folder (Box 286, Folder 11)
      - C. F. - Calvert, 1895-1913; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 1)
      - Calvert, Charles Benedict, 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 2)
      - Calvert County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 3)
      - Camp - Carmichael, 1903-1913; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 4)
      - Caroline County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 5)
      - Caroline County - Carroll County, 1899-1918; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 6)
      - Carroll County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 7)
      - Carter - Causey, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 8)
      - Cecil County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 9)
      - Cecil County: miscellaneous, 1908-1918; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 10)
      - Central National Bank of Frederick, Maryland, 1912-1913; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 11)
      - Chaisty - Chapman, 1908-1912; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 12)
      - Charles County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 13)
      - Chen - Chevy Chase Association, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 14)
      - Chevy Chase Incorporation, 1912; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 15)
      - Chew - Civic, 1894-1915; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 16)
      - Clagatt - Clayton, 1896-1917; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 17)
      - Cleaveland - Coleman, 1896-1915; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 18)
      - Collamer - Combs, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 287, Folder 19)
      - Committee of One Hundred: regarding William Jennings Bryan election, 1908; 1 folder (Box 288, Folder 1)
      - Committee - Cooke, 1901-1915; 1 folder (Box 288, Folder 2)
      - Coolahan, John T. - Coyne, 1897-1913; 1 folder (Box 288, Folder 3)
      - Craddock - Craycroft, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 288, Folder 4)
      - Credit - Cutts, undated; 1 folder (Box 288, Folder 5)
      - Dadds - Davis, 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 1)
      - Dawkins - Democratic Association, 1897-1916; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 2)
      - Democratic Auxiliary Committee, 1912; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 3)
      - Democratic Congressional Committee, 1896-1900; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 4)
      - Democratic Executive Committee (Alleghany County, MD), 1896; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 5)
      - Democratic.. .miscellaneous, 1898-1913; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 6)
      - Democratic National Committee, 1900-1912; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 7)
      - Democratic Party, Governing Body of The, 1911-1912; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 8)
      - Democratic State Central Committee (headquarters in Baltimore), 1900-1910; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 9)
      - Democratic State Central Committee headquarters: miscellaneous, 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 10)
      - Democratic State Central Committee headquarters rooms, 1896-1898; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 11)
      - Denmead - Disharoon, 1900-1915; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 12)
      - District of Columbia - Miscellaneous, 1893-1917; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 13)
      - Dixon - Doolittle, 1897-1919; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 1)
      - Dorchester County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 2)
      - Dorfler - Dugan, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 3)
      - Dulany-Vernay Co. - Dyson, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 4)
      - Eakle - Eustis, 1898-1915; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 1)
      - Evans - Ewing, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 2)
      - F. S. - Fidler, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 3)
      - Field, S. S, 1901-1917; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 4)
      - Fields - Frederick Board of Trade, 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 5)
      - Frederick County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 6)
      - Frederick County: miscellaneous, 1911-1913; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 7)
      - Free - Furst, 1896-1917; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 8)
      - Gadsby - Garner, 1906-1918; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 9)
      - Garrett County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 10)
      - Garrett, John A, 1909-1913; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 11)
      - "The Garrett Journal", 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 12)
      - Garrett: miscellaneous, 1908-1915; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 13)
      - Garrott: "The Gazette", 1902-1913; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 14)
      - Geare - Goldsborough, T., 1896-1917; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 1)
      - Goldsborough, W. W, 1906-1913; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 2)
      - Goldsmith - Gorsuch, 1900-1913; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 3)
      - Goslin, E. E, 1910-1913; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 4)
      - Gott - Gray, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 5)
      - Greager - Grove, H. B., 1904-1915; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 6)
      - Grove, William J, 1905-1917; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 7)
      - Grover - Guy, 1907-1918; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 8)
      - Hackett - Hale, 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 9)
      - Haley, Hardy J, 1907-1911; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 10)
      - Hall - Hambleton, 1903-1914; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 11)
      - Hamill, G. Semmes, 1908-1915; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 12)
      - Hamill, J. D. - Hardy, 1896-1917; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 13)
      - Harford County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 14)
      - "The Harford Democrat", 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 15)
      - Hargis - Hartigan, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 16)
      - Hartle & Wolfinger, 1912-1913; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 17)
      - Henderson, B. H. - Henderson, H. I., 1905-1918; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 1)
      - Henderson, J. Alby, 1909-1913; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 2)
      - Henderson, J. B. - Hennaman, 1898-1917; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 3)
      - Henry, W. Laird, 1911-1913; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 4)
      - Henry, W. F. - Higdon, 1896-1917; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 5)
      - Higgins - Hilton, D. W., 1899-1923; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 6)
      - Hilton, R. G, 1906-1913; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 7)
      - Hinchman - Howard, Charles H., 1896-1914; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 8)
      - Howard County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 9)
      - Howard, H. - Hunt, 1906-1918; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 10)
      - Huritt - Hyde, T., 1900-1923; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 11)
      - Ihmsen, M. F, 1900; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 12)
      - Im - Iv (general), 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 13)
      - J. H. - Janin, 1904-1913; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 1)
      - Janney, John H, 1900-1913; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 2)
      - Jarman, John F, 1913; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 3)
      - Jarrell - Johnston, 1900-1917; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 4)
      - Jones, A. - Jones, W., 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 5)
      - Jordan - Just, 1898-1913; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 6)
      - Kahn, I. S, 1912-1913; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 7)
      - Kaiser - Keiser, 1897-1917; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 8)
      - Keller, George, 1902; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 9)
      - Kemble - Kensington, 1902-1917; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 10)
      - Kent County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 11)
      - Kent, N. - Knell, 1905-1917; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 12)
      - Knight, M. D, 1905-1910; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 13)
      - Knorr - Krep, 1900-1917; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 14)
      - Labor - Lakeland, 1892-1912; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 1)
      - Lamar, George H. (1867-1945), 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 2)
      - Lamar, W. H. (1859-1928), 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 3)
      - Lambert - Layton, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 4)
      - League - LeCompte, 1899-1916; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 5)
      - Lee, Blair: miscellaneous, 1901-1913; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 6)
      - Lee, C. - Leonard, 1900-1913; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 7)
      - Leser, Oscar, 1906-1913; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 8)
      - Levin - Lewin, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 9)
      - Lewis, David J. (1869-1952), 1900-1910; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 10)
      - Lewis, E. D. - Littauer, 1896-1915; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 11)
      - Little, C. A., 1900-1913; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 12)
      - Little, P. - Log, 1899-1912; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 13)
      - Long, Albert, 1912-1913; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 14)
      - Long, C. - Lyons, 1897-1913; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 15)
      - Mace - Mahony, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 1)
      - Main - Marbury, 1910-1918; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 2)
      - Maryland, D., 1899-1919; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 3)
      - Maryland, G. - Maryland, T., 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 4)
      - Maryland, State of, 1886-1919; 6 folders
        - Executive Department, 1886-1919; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 5)
        - Geological Survey, 1905-1912; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 6)
        - Secretary of State, 1896-1911; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 7)
        - State Board of Health, 1911-1913; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 8)
        - State: miscellaneous, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 9)
        - State Roads Commission, 1909-1913; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 1)
      - Mason - Maynard, 1901-1912; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 2)
      - McAdoo - McGrew, 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 3)
      - McGuire, Philip M, 1902-1912; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 4)
      - McIntosh - McReynolds, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 5)
      - McSherry, J. Roger, 1896; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 6)
      - Merchants & Manufacturers Association, 1910-1913; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 7)
      - Merchants National Bank - Meyers, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 8)
      - Michael - Miles, 1909-1917; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 9)
      - Miller - Mitchell, 1905-1915; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 10)
      - Mobley - Montgomery, 1905-1917; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 11)
      - Montgomery County, 1893-1917; 7 folders
        - Board of County Commissioners, 1893-1912; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 12)
        - Board of County School Commissioners, 1906-1915; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 13)
        - Board of Supervisors of Election, 1906-1911; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 14)
        - Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 15)
        - Miscellaneous, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 1)
        - Office of the Road Superintendent, 1910-1917; 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 2)
        - Office of the Road Superintendent (Merrill D. Knight), undated; 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 3)
      - Moody - Mother, 1900-1917; 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 4)
      - Motter Brothers & Co. (Guy Kunkel Motter and S. L. Motter), 1912-1913; 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 5)
      - Mount - Myers, 1900-1917; 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 6)
      - Nagengast - National Anti, 1900-1909; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 1)
      - National Association of Democratic Clubs, 1897-1904; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 2)
      - National Association of Railway... - National Democratic, 1896-1912; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 3)
      - National Federation for People's Rule, 1907; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 4)
      - National Guard, 1917; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 5)
      - National Independent - Newman, 1896-1914; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 6)
      - Nicholson - Nugent, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 7)
      - O'Donnell - Order of Knights, 1900-1913; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 8)
      - Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1906-1912; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 9)
      - Orem - Owens, Edward T., 1902-1912; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 10)
      - Owens, James W, 1908-1918; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 11)
      - Owens, John W. - Oysters, 1911-1913; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 12)
      - Paca - Parke, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 1)
      - Parkins - Peter, A., 1902-1917; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 2)
      - Peter, Edward C, 1901- 1910; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 3)
      - Peter, Robert - Piper, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 4)
      - Plant - Poffenberger, G., 1902-1913; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 5)
      - Poffenberger, T. A., 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 6)
      - Pogue, J. A, 1910-1913; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 7)
      - Polk - Price, 1896-1915; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 8)
      - Prince George's County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 9)
      - Prince George's County: County Commissioners (Pullman), 1897-1917; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 10)
      - Pumphrey - Pyle, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 11)
      - Q (general), 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 1)
      - Raborg - Rayner, Albert W., 1903-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 2)
      - Rayner, Isidor, 1908-1912; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 3)
      - Rayner, W. B. - Retail, 1907-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 4)
      - Reynolds - Rhein, 1901-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 5)
      - Rhodes & Rhodes, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 6)
      - Rice - Risdon, 1898-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 7)
      - Roach - Roys, 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 8)
      - Ruckle - Ryon, 1900-1918; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 9)
      - Sacks - Sawyer, 1896-1917; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 10)
      - Scaggs - Sewall, 1893-1917; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 11)
      - Shafer - Shuman, 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 12)
      - Sibley - Sisson, 1899-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 13)
      - Slay, William, 1911-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 14)
      - Small - Smith, E., 1906-1912; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 15)
      - Smith, Frank O, 1911-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 16)
      - Smith, G. - Smoot, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 17)
      - Snouffer - Somers, 1912-1917; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 1)
      - Somerset County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 2)
      - Somerset County (miscellaneous): southern, 1900-1913; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 3)
      - Sowers - Spring, 1896-1919; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 4)
      - St. Bernard's - St. Mary's County (Register of Wills), 1911-1915; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 5)
      - St. Mary's County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 6)
      - Stabler - Steck, 1900-1915; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 7)
      - Steele, Guy W, 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 8)
      - Stellwagon - Stevens, 1906-1915; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 9)
      - Stevenson - Stonestreet, 1900-1913; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 10)
      - Story - Sullivan, 1896-1913; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 11)
      - The Sun, 1896-1915; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 12)
      - Sundergill - Symons, 1908-1918; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 13)
      - Tablen - Talbot County (miscellaneous), 1888-1912; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 14)
      - Talbot County: Maryland Gubernatorial Race, 1911; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 15)
      - Talbott - Thomas, D., 1896-1915; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 16)
      - Thomas, E. P, 1897-1914; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 1)
      - Thomas, G. - Thomson, 1902-1918; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 2)
      - Tilghman - Townshend, 1896-1917; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 3)
      - Travelers and Merchants' Association - Tull, 1899-1913; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 4)
      - Turner, J. Frank, 1907-1913; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 5)
      - Turner - Tyson, 1906-1913; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 6)
      - Uhde - Usilton, 1900-1918; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 7)
      - United States, 1898-1920; 10 folders
        - Civil Service Commission, 1905-1913; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 8)
        - Department of Agriculture, 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 9)
        - Department of Commerce (United States Fuel Administration), 1913-1918; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 10)
        - Department of the Interior, 1903-1913; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 11)
        - Department of Justice - Department of State, 1899-1920; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 12)
        - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1909-1911; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 13)
        - Navy - Marine Corps, 1898-1920; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 14)
        - Postmaster General - Supreme Court, 1902-1913; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 15)
        - Treasury Department, 1907-1917; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 16)
        - War Department, 1906-1915; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 17)
      - United States House of Representatives, 1890-1917; 3 folders
        - A-Z (general), 1890-1912; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 1)
        - David J. Lewis (1869-1952), 1911-1913; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous Committees, 1897-1917; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 3)
      - United States Senate, 1896-1918; 4 folders
        - A-Z (general), 1897-1913; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous Committees, 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 5)
        - Isidor Raynor (1850-1912), 1906-1911; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 6)
        - John Walter Smith (1845-1925), 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 7)
      - V (general), 1896-1919; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 8)
      - W - Ware, 1897-1919; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 9)
      - Warfield - Washington, 1898-1918; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 10)
      - Waters, Bowie, 1896-1910; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 11)
      - Waters - Webster, 1900-1918; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 12)
      - The Weekly Chronicle, 1910-1913; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 13)
      - Weem - Westcott, 1896-1919; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 14)
      - Western - Whyte, 1898-1916; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 1)
      - Wickes - Williams, John S., 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 2)
      - Williams, John W, 1905-1912; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 3)
      - Williams, R. - Wilson, William, 1896-1917; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 4)
      - Wilson, Woodrow, 1911-1917; 6 folders
        - Wilson, Woodrow, 1911-1917; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 5)
        - Wilson, Woodrow: A-Z (general), 1912; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 6)
        - Wilson, Woodrow: Campaign Committee, 1912; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 7)
        - Wilson, Woodrow: Democratic Association, 1911-1912; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 8)
        - Wilson, Woodrow: Headquarters, 1912; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 9)
        - Wilson, Woodrow: Marshall Clubs, 1912; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 10)
      - Windham - Worthington, E., 1908-1913; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 11)
      - Worthington, Glenn H, 1906-1913; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 12)
      - Y (general), 1903-1913; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 13)
      - Z (general), 1902-1912; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 14)
      - Unidentified, 1909-1915; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 15)
    - Legal and Business: A-Z, 1843-1923; 12 boxes
      Contains letters pertaining to legal cases, real estate, investments, and banking.
      - A - American, 1887-1909; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 1)